[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 53? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "8820.26",
      "options": [
        "8823.26",
        "8818.76",
        "8820.26",
        "8821.76"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 57? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "10201.86",
      "options": [
        "10200.36",
        "10201.86",
        "10203.36",
        "10204.86"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 18? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1017.36",
      "options": [
        "1017.36",
        "1020.36",
        "1018.86",
        "1015.86"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 28? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2461.76",
      "options": [
        "2460.26",
        "2464.76",
        "2461.76",
        "2463.26"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 24? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1808.64",
      "options": [
        "1811.64",
        "1808.64",
        "1807.14",
        "1810.14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 28? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2461.76",
      "options": [
        "2460.26",
        "2464.76",
        "2461.76",
        "2463.26"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 26? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2122.64",
      "options": [
        "2125.64",
        "2124.14",
        "2122.64",
        "2121.14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 26? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2122.64",
      "options": [
        "2124.14",
        "2121.14",
        "2122.64",
        "2125.64"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 29? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2640.74",
      "options": [
        "2642.24",
        "2640.74",
        "2639.24",
        "2643.74"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 39? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "4775.94",
      "options": [
        "4777.44",
        "4778.94",
        "4775.94",
        "4774.44"
      ]
    }
]